## Ivanchuk Ivan

(+7) 988-061-84-72 | l3r8y@duck.com | t.me.l3r8y | blog | github.com/l3r8yJ | linkedin

## Experience

Samokat.tech | Kotlin Backend Developer | 23.10.2023 - present.

Working on the clients tickets system. Developed a few OSS products during the working in project.
Kotlin, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Gradle, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase, Jooq

VTB | Java Team Lead | 30.08.2023 - 23.10.2023.

• Integration of banking systems. Work on CRM for the banking segment. Managing a team of 8 people. Java 11, Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase

VTB | Java Developer | 03.04.2023 - 30.08.2023.

• Integration of banking systems. Work on CRM for the banking segment.

Java 11, Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Apache Kafka, RabbitMQ, PostgreSQL, Liquibase

Open Source | Java developer | 24.06.2022 - present.

• R&D development. Worked on code quality control tools, eolang programming language, maven plugins Java, Maven, XSL, Docker, Unit Testing, Integration Testing, Rust, Ruby, EO, LATEX

INTERVOLGA | 19.04.2022 - 04.08.2022

• B2B development. Worked on integration of 1c-bitrix PHP, 1c-bitrix framework, SQL

Freelance | Java developer | May 2021 - April 2022

• Development of telegram bots for trading cryptocurrency platform Java, TelegramBots, Spring, SpringBoot, SpringData, Docker

#### Skills

- Java, Kotlin | Spring Boot, Spring Data, Spring Security, Spring Cloud, Spring WebFlux, Maven, Gradle, Liquibase
- RDBMS | PostgreSQL
- CI/CD | Openshift, K8s, TeamCity, Docker, GitHub Actions, rultor, 0pdd
- VCS | Git, GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket
- Other | Ruby, Rust

#### Languages

English | B1 intermediate

Russian | C1 native

### Education

### Volgograd State Technical University

Bachelor, Engineering and Economics, Software engineering

2020 - 2024

#### Courses and etc.

Completely self-taught by reading books and practicing a lot.

I also have a small blog about software, perhaps it will be of interest to you. [link]

# About

I have my own open source projects, one of them is a Ruby library. It has reached **9k+ downloads**. You can find it and other projects or contributions in my <u>GitHub account</u>. Also I'm contributing in different open source projects. I am highly interested in the development of R&D and OSS, have experience in conducting research and publishing scientific papers, also have experience in developing programming language, maven plugins, static analysis and quality control tools. I have experience in teaching students in the discipline *Theory of Formal Languages*. Also, member of jury <u>KaiCode</u> OSS festival.